Guide to the War Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- World War I, 1914-1918; Series I
  - Lafon Allen Collection
    - United States of America
      - For Home and Country. Victory Liberty Loan., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0391; 20x30 inches (Box 141)
      - V. Invest., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0392; 20x30 inches (Box 141)
      - Victory Liberty Loan., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0393; 99x99 inches (Box 141)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: United States. In 3 pieces.
      - For a Peace of Prosperity and Plenty, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0394; 99x99 inches (Box 141)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: United States. In 5 pieces.
      - Honor Button. Every American Should Consider It an Honor to Wear, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0395; 11x14 inches (Box 141)
      - Untitled, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0396; 99x99 inches (Box 142)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: United States. In 9 pieces.
      - They Finished Their Job. Now Let's Finish Ours, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0397; 14x20 inches (Box 142)
      - Victory Liberty Loan. Let's Finish the Job., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0398; 99x99 inches (Box 142)
      - The Victory Loan Flyers. Watch for the Airplane Special, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0399; 20x30 inches (Box 142)
        Artist: Watkins, K.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Americans All!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0400; 27x40 inches (Box 142)
        Artist: Christy Howard Chandler. Place of Publication: United States.
      - They Kept the Sea Lanes Open, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0401; 39x29 inches (Box 142)
      - They Gave Their All Forever. You Are Asked to Lend for a While., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0402; 99x99 inches (Box 142)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: United States. In 2 pieces.
      - Stand Behind the Country's Girlhood. Y.M.C.A. New York's Share, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0403; 20x30 inches (Box 143)
        Artist: Benda, W.T.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Welcome, Soldiers, Sailors and Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0404; 28x44 inches (Box 143)
      - Banish Lonely Hours in Camp. Help Provide Libraries Filled, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0405; 29x42 inches (Box 143)
      - Saving Daylight. An Hour of Light for an Hour of Night, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0406; 40x27 inches (Box 143)
      - Saving Daylight. Sign and Mail one of these Postcards, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0407; 40x27 inches (Box 143)
      - Memorial Day, May 30th, 1917, AUS0408; 40x26 inches (Box 143)
      - 140th Flag Day; 1777-1917, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0409; 26x40 inches (Box 143)
      - E Pluribus Unum., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0410; 40x26 inches (Box 143)
      - Your Country Calls. Enlist - Plow - Buy Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0411; 22x28 inches (Box 143)
        Artist: Myers, Lloyd. Place of Publication: United States.
      - A Longer Day of Daylight for the Man with the Gun and the Man, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0412; 40x26 inches (Box 143)
      - Welcome, Comrade at Arms., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0413; 26x40 inches (Box 143)
      - Welcome, Noble Belgium., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0414; 20x40 inches (Box 143)
      - Saving Daylight. Gain an Hour of Daylight, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0415; 20x40 inches (Box 143)
      - Wanted at Once - Men and Boys Who Have Had Actual Farm Experience, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0416; 17x24 inches (Box 143)
      - Hurry! Cull Your Hens, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0417; 20x28 inches (Box 143)
      - Hero Land, 1917 November-December; AUS0418; 28x41 inches (Box 143)
        Artist: Mueller, J. Carl. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Hero Land, 1917 November-December; AUS0419; 28x41 inches (Box 143)
      - Hero Land, 1917 November-December; AUS0420; 14x22 inches (Box 143)
        Artist: Rapeno, A.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Can You Drive a Car? Will You Drive One in France?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0421; 14x23 inches (Box 144)
      - Proclamation! To the Citizens of New York: Upon Just Grounds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0422; 12x18 inches (Box 144)
      - No War Talk! Attorney - General Gregory Says: "Obey the Law..", Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0423; 14x08 inches (Box 144)
      - They Signal, "Send Books..", Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0424; 25x38 inches (Box 144)
      - Books Wanted for Our Men in Camp and "Over There..", Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0425; 28x42 inches (Box 144)
      - How Can I Help My Country?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0426; 22x28 inches (Box 144)
      - I Have a Boy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0427; 19x33 inches (Box 144)
        Artist: McMein, Neysa Moran. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Why We Are at War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0428; 18x22 inches (Box 144)
      - A Message to the Men and Women of Connecticut, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0429; 14x22 inches (Box 144)
      - Patriotic Farm Census, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0430; 14x23 inches (Box 144)
      - Do Your Bit. Help Win the War. Grow a Garden, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0431; 11x14 inches (Box 144)
      - Men in the Draft: Your Country Provides War Risk Insurance, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0432; 14x22 inches (Box 144)
      - Help! The Women's Land Army of America, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0433; 27x41 inches (Box 144)
        Artist: Givson, Charles Dana. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Your President and Your Governor Endorse the, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0434; 21x29 inches (Box 144)
      - Send Sammy Smilage, $1.00, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0435; 19x29 inches (Box 144)
      - Help the Horse and Save the Soldier, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0436; 20x30 inches (Box 144)
        Artist: Matania, F.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Help Him to Help Us, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0437; 23x33 inches (Box 144)
      - The Ten Commandments of Womanhood. Nineteen Hundred and Eighteen, 1918; AUS0438; 14x21 inches (Box 144)
      - Missouri Leads in Food Increase, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0439; 24x36 inches (Box 144)
      - Your Country Appeals for Humanity, Join the Red Star, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0440; 28x42 inches (Box 144)
      - Do Your Bit for the Faithful War Horse, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0441; 28x42 inches (Box 145)
      - Horses Transport All Munitions from Supply Bases to Trench, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0442; 28x42 inches (Box 145)
      - American Horses and Mules Are Fighting. They Fight on the Firing, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0443; 28x42 inches (Box 145)
      - All Food Supplies Are Carried to the Men in the Trenches by Horses., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0444; 28x42 inches (Box 145)
      - The Work That You Do Every Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0445; 22x28 inches (Box 145)
      - What Doth It Prophet a Man?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0446; 14x22 inches (Box 145)
      - Why Germany Wants Peace Now, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0447; 42x28 inches (Box 145)
      - Courage, Comrades, I Am Coming, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0448; 28x42 inches (Box 145)
        Artist: Jonas, Lucien - Hector. Place of Publication: United States.
      - American Red Star Animal Relief, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0449; 22x32 inches (Box 145)
      - Wanted 25,000 Student Nurses, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0450; 28x42 inches (Box 145)
      - The Past Is Behind Us, the Future Is Ahead, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0451; 15x20 inches (Box 145)
      - America's Tribute to Britain, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0452; 20x30 inches (Box 145)
        Artist: C., F. G.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Britain's Day, Dec. 7, 1918, 1918 December; AUS0453; 10x15 inches (Box 145)
      - War Information No charge, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0454; 20x30 inches (Box 145)
      - For Our Aviators Send Us Something to Melt or Sell, Gold, Silver, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0455; 30x40 inches (Box 145)
      - Treat 'em Rough! Join the Tanks., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0456; 28x41 inches (Box 145)
        Artist: Nutaf, August. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Let us Carry on This Work Until We End All War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0457; 26x41 inches (Box 145)
      - Save Serbia, Our Ally, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0458; 24x36 inches (Box 145)
        Artist: Steinlen, Theophile Alexandre. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Britain's Day, Dec. 7, 1918, 1918 December; AUS0459; 27x40 inches (Box 145)
      - Service. Fall In!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0460; 17x25 inches (Box 145)
        Artist: Patterson, Lucille. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Women's Land Army of America, 1918; AUS0461; 20x30 inches (Box 145)
      - We Deliver the Goods S.O.S., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0462; 30x45 inches (Box 145)
        Artist: NcNein, Neysa. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Save Your Child From Autocracy and Poverty., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0463; 29x40 inches (Box 145)
      - Halt the Hun!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0464; 52x43 inches (Box 145)
        Artist: Raleigh. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Help Stop This., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0465; 21x28 inches (Box 146)
      - Food Conservation Week. Your Patriotism, Your Loyalty, 1918 December; AUS0466; 11x17 inches (Box 146)
      - Notice of Enlistment National War Savings Army, 1918 June; AUS0467; 40x55 inches (Box 146)
      - This Couldn't Happen!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0468; 22x28 inches (Box 146)
      - After the Welcome Home - a Job!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0469; 28x42 inches (Box 146)
      - Sing for Victory Thanksgiving Day., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0470; 41x28 inches (Box 146)
      - The A.E.F. to the President; To the Folks Back Home, 1918 September 28; AUS0471; 33x23 inches (Box 147)
      - Do You Know This Yank? These Men are Dying for You, 1918 September 28; AUS0472; 33x23 inches (Box 147)
      - The Child at Your Door...Save the Survivors., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0473; 55x36 inches (Box 147)
      - Give Your Share: One Campaign, 1919; AUS0474; 21x28 inches (Box 147)
      - 1919 War Chest., AUS0475; 14x21 inches (Box 147)
        Artist: Almars, J.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - 1919 War Chest. 10 Funds in One., AUS0476; 58x41 inches (Box 147)
      - 1919 War Chest. Give Your Share., AUS0477; 41x28 inches (Box 147)
      - The United States Government Has Asked Us to help, 1917; AUS0478; 16x24 inches (Box 147)
      - All About Liberty Bonds., 1917; AUS0479; 21x27 inches (Box 147)
      - World Pictures: The Road to France., 1917; AUS0480; 21x27 inches (Box 147)
      - World Pictures: The Road to France., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0481; 28x41 inches (Box 147)
      - The Second Official United States War Picture. America's Answer, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0482; 28x42 inches (Box 147)
      - Now For Some Music. Draft Your Slacker Records, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0483; 19x29 inches (Box 147)
      - Stage Women's War Relief., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0484; 22x31 inches (Box 147)
      - This Church is Behind the United War Work Campaign, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0485; 19x25 inches (Box 147)
      - Contest: Friars vs. Lambs for United War Work Campaign, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0486; 44x87 inches (Box 147)
      - Y.W.C.A., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0487; 33x36 inches (Box 148)
      - Y.W.C.A., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0488; 17x23 inches (Box 148)
      - My Patriotic Duty is Red Cross Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0489; 14x11 inches (Box 148)
        Artist: Iciek, S.A.; McCoy, Arthur G.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Wanted: Husky Young Americans...It's a Dare! Join the Tanks., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0490; 19x25 inches (Box 148)
        Artist: Hoffman, W.F.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - All Those Who Long to Wear Our Country's Coat...Join the Tanks., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0491; 19x25 inches (Box 148)
      - The U.S. Air Service Needs Machinists, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0492; 22x14 inches (Box 148)
      - Uphold Our Honor. Join Army-Navy-Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0493; 21x11 inches (Box 148)
      - Volunteers for 1st Kentucky: Jump In., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0494; 30x06 inches (Box 148)
      - Treat 'em Rough! Join the Tanks., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0495; 11x14 inches (Box 148)
        Artist: Hutaf, Angie T.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The U.S. Air Service Needs Carpenters, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0496; 22x14 inches (Box 148)
      - Join Here., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0497; 20x31 inches (Box 148)
      - The Motor Corps of America., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0498; 30x40 inches (Box 148)
        Artist: Jones, Helene. Place of Publication: United States.
      - 7 Morale., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0499; 28x11 inches (Box 148)
      - 7 and 1 Give! One Year to Get Our Boys Home Keep Them Well., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0500; 14x41 inches (Box 148)
      - To the Last Cent - To the Last Man - To the Last Heartbeat, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0501; 19x23 inches (Box 148)
      - Help Fill the War Chest: Humanity Calls., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0502; 17x18 inches (Box 148)
        Artist: Osnis, B.A.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Give All in One Hat., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0503; 17x24 inches (Box 148)
  - Yale University Library Collection
    - United States of America
      - NAVY! Uncle Sam is Calling You! Enlist in the Navy! DO IT NOW!, 1917; YUS0001; 11x14 inches (Box 149)
      - A Good Navy must have the Best Men. Don't Delay. Enlist Today., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0002; 11x14 inches (Box 149)
      - U.S. Navy. See the World! Save Your Money! Serve the Nation!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0003; 21x11 inches (Box 149)
      - These Men Have Come Across. They Are at the Front Now, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0004; 21x11 inches (Box 149)
        Artist: Leyendecker, P. X.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Join These Men and Do Your Share in Keeping Your Country Safe, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0005; 21x11 inches (Box 149)
      - Help Wanted! The Navy's Job is to Put 'em Across. Only Young Men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0006; 14x21 inches (Box 149)
        Artist: Scott, R.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Follow the Flag for Freedom. Your Choice, Naval Reserve, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0007; 14x22 inches (Box 149)
      - Only the Navy Can Stop This., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0008; 19x25 inches (Box 149)
        Artist: Rogers, W.A.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Follow the Boys in Blue for Home and Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0009; 29x22 inches (Box 149)
      - Will You Supply Eyes for the Navy? Navy Ships Need Binoculars, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0010; 21x29 inches (Box 149)
      - Who Takes Sammy to France? The Man Behind the Man Behind the Gun!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0011; 21x28 inches (Box 149)
      - Come On You Sea-Cooks...Enlist in Naval Reserve Force, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0012; 21x28 inches (Box 149)
      - Women Awake! Your Country Needs You. Learn to be of National, 1916; YUS0013; 19x25 inches (Box 149)
        Artist: Roberts, Hazel. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Service for Traning and Travel. Ages 17 to 35. Join the Navy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0014; 30x23 inches (Box 149)
      - Come Along. Learn something, see something in the U.S. Navy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0015; 28x42 inches (Box 149)
      - Shall Uncle Sam's Navy Suffer Our Soldiers Going, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0016; 28x42 inches (Box 150)
      - I Shall Expect Every Man Who Is Not a Slacker to be at My Side, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0017; 29x43 inches (Box 150)
      - You Wireless Fans, Help the Navy Get the Hun Submarine, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0018; 28x43 inches (Box 150)
        Artist: Falls, C.B.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - A Wonderful Opportunity for You, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0019; 20x36 inches (Box 150)
        Artist: Ruttan. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Give the World the Once Over in the United States Navy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0020; 28x42 inches (Box 150)
      - U.S. Navy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0021; 28x42 inches (Box 150)
      - Reserves - the Navy is calling for 100,000 Men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0022; 28x42 inches (Box 150)
      - Navy Men Needed Now, 1917; YUS0023; 25x38 inches (Box 150)
      - The menace Grows. Enlist Now., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0024; 16x22 inches (Box 150)
      - Join the Army Air Service. Be An American Eagle!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0025; 21x27 inches (Box 150)
      - Join the Air Service. "Give 'er the Gun." Learn-Earn., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0026; 20x30 inches (Box 151)
        Artist: Keith, W.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Men Wanted for the Army., 1914; YUS0027; 29x40 inches (Box 151)
        Artist: Hazelton, B.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Even a Dog Enlists. Why Not you?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0028; 28x42 inches (Box 151)
      - They Mutilate - For Humanity's Sake Enlist., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0029; 26x40 inches (Box 151)
        Artist: Beringer. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Men Wanted for the Army., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0030; 28x40 inches (Box 151)
        Artist: Nelson, Michael P.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Teamwork Wins! With Your Help They are Invincible, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0031; 28x42 inches (Box 151)
        Artist: Still, Roy Hull. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Another Notch Chateau Thierry. U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0032; 30x40 inches (Box 151)
      - U.S. Marines. Soldiers of the Sea., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0033; 30x40 inches (Box 151)
      - Men Wanted. U.S. Marines. Two-in-One-Service, 1916; YUS0034; 30x40 inches (Box 151)
        Artist: Westervelt, Walter M.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - U.S. Marines. "Soldiers of the Sea." Good Pay, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0035; 30x40 inches (Box 151)
      - This Device on Hat or Helmet Means U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0036; 28x41 inches (Box 152)
      - For Active Service Join the U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0037; 18x25 inches (Box 152)
      - For Active Service Join the U.S. Marines., 1913; YUS0038; 18x25 inches (Box 152)
      - For Active Service Join the U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0039; 18x25 inches (Box 152)
      - Go Over the Top with U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0040; 21x28 inches (Box 152)
      - An Opportunity to See the World. Foreign Travel. Good Pay, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0041; 18x25 inches (Box 152)
        Artist: Moore, Bruce. Place of Publication: United States.
      - We Have Given. Second War Fund., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0042; 08x12 inches (Box 152)
      - Untitled., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0043; 08x12 inches (Box 152)
      - Every Man! Must Register for the Selective Service Draft, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0044; 23x35 inches (Box 152)
      - New York American. Draft Questionnaire Information Sheet., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0045; 17x31 inches (Box 152)
      - Registration...12th Day of September 1918., 1918 September 12; YUS0046; 14x11 inches (Box 152)
      - The Motor Corps of America., 1918; YUS0047; 33x42 inches (Box 152)
      - Learn to Ride...First Field Artillery. New York Guard., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0048; 28x41 inches (Box 152)
      - Yes Sir. I am Here. Recruits Wanted. Motor Corps of America., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0049; 27x40 inches (Box 152)
      - Stenographers Wanted...Ordinance Department of Washington D.C., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0050; 19x25 inches (Box 152)
      - Which? Soldier or Mechanic. Enlist in the First Replacement, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0051; 17x23 inches (Box 153)
      - Britishers and Canadians ...Enlist Today. British and Canadian, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0052; 20x30 inches (Box 153)
      - Engineers. Blaze the Trail for Liberty. The First Replacement, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0053; 18x23 inches (Box 153)
      - Automobile Drivers Do Your Bit! Drive a Motortruck for Uncle Sam, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0054; 14x22 inches (Box 153)
      - U.S. Mariners. "Soldiers of the Sea.", Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0055; 30x40 inches (Box 153)
      - A Man from this House is Fighting in France with United States, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0056; 11x14 inches (Box 153)
      - Your Country Calls. Join the Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0057; 11x06 inches (Box 153)
      - A Man from this House is Serving in the U.S. Marine Corps., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0058; 14x10 inches (Box 153)
      - Important! Information for Registered Men. Men Who Registered, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0059; 14x16 inches (Box 153)
      - Join the Marines. If You Want Action, Get Under This., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0060; 14x22 inches (Box 153)
        Artist: Lozier, Gladys. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Americans! Join and Fight! U.S. Army., 1918; YUS0061; 28x42 inches (Box 153)
        Artist: de la Laing, Edward. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Combination that Will Win the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0062; 28x42 inches (Box 153)
      - The Call to Duty. Join the Army for Home and Country., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0063; 30x40 inches (Box 153)
        Artist: Cammilli, Edoardo. Place of Publication: United States.
      - They Crucify. American Manhood, Enlist., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0064; 28x42 inches (Box 153)
        Artist: Hoyle, M.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Going... Going... Gone, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0065; 29x42 inches (Box 153)
      - Not Just Hats Off for the Flag, but Sleves Up for It., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0066; 28x42 inches (Box 154)
        Artist: Palmer, A.H.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Five Thousand by June. Graduate Nurses Your Country Needs You., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0067; 20x28 inches (Box 154)
        Artist: Rakeman, C.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - How to Send Mail, Money, and Parcels to Prisoners in Germany, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0068; 17x22 inches (Box 154)
      - Nurses. The Call from No Man's Land is "Come Across.", Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0069; 21x28 inches (Box 154)
      - Young Women! Nurses are Needed. You Are Needed too, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0070; 21x28 inches (Box 154)
      - America called her men to fight. She Now calls her women., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0071; 21x28 inches (Box 154)
      - Nurses of America! The Lives of our soldiers and sailors, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0072; 21x28 inches (Box 154)
      - Second Red Cross War Fund., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0073; 22x32 inches (Box 154)
      - He Can Win. The Federal Board Provides Training, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0074; 19x27 inches (Box 154)
        Artist: Smith, Dan. Place of Publication: United States.
      - You Can Help. American Red Cross., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0075; 20x30 inches (Box 154)
      - American Red Cross. Our Boys Need Sox. Knit Your bit., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0076; 20x30 inches (Box 154)
      - Put Fighting Blood in Your Business. Here's His Record, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0077; 28x19 inches (Box 154)
      - Join the Red Cross, and on Christmas eve, a candle in every, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0078; 21x11 inches (Box 154)
      - Make good the promise. Keep it full over here, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0079; 21x11 inches (Box 154)
      - Help Your Red Cross. "Inasmuch as ye have done it unto one of, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0080; 14x22 inches (Box 154)
        Artist: Chapin, Hubert. Place of Publication: United States.